<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Michael Neil</title>
    <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Michael Neil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 19:56:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Supervisord Docker and Loggly</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/supervisord-docker-and-loggly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 19:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/supervisord-docker-and-loggly/</guid>
      <description>99% of what I need to do can be found on Stack Overflow. But, I had a hard time finding any article that explained how to put together Supervisord and Docker and pipe the logs into Loggly.
This week I had the pleasure of dealing with log aggregation from multiple docker containers. I use Docker quite often. I find that private registries make it easy to distribute images to my team, and my servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MnCombine WP Plugin Release</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/mncombine-wp-plugin-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 23:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/mncombine-wp-plugin-release/</guid>
      <description>MnCombine WP Plugin Release MnCombine Asset Management Plugin!
I’ll cut to the chase. I love the WordPress community and there are plenty of cache/asset management/css compressors/javascript compilers out there. So why the $#!! would I write another one? Simple, because this one is obviously the best! I use the same technique all the time to management my javascript and css files. Monitor changes to the file on request, hash the files needed along with the times they were updated, look for a file if it exists or generate a new one then load it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dealing With Credit Card Gateways</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/dealing-with-credit-card-gateways/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 22:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/dealing-with-credit-card-gateways/</guid>
      <description>Dealing With Credit Card Gateways I’ve processed thousands of credit card payments. Well, not me really, but my code has. And in doing so I’ve started to find a flow; a list if you will, of things that you absolutely must do to keep your visitor’s heads from exploding when trying to send you money!
Make It Easy
But what does that mean? Everyone knows that people tend to take the easy route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stripe Credit Card Processing : Thoughts?</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/stripe-credit-card-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 06:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/stripe-credit-card-processing/</guid>
      <description>Stripe Credit Card Processing : Thoughts? If you don’t know, now you know:
https://stripe.com/
Stripe is, or rather states, that they do online processing for a flat fee and act as your gateway interfacing directly with your bank. AWESOME! I think Stripe is pretty new right now; and unfortunately I haven’t used them to know how great it really is. But, I’ve built enough online stores to know that online transactions are cumbersome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chop A String On a Whole Word With PHP</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/php-chop-string-on-whole-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 00:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/php-chop-string-on-whole-word/</guid>
      <description>Chop A String On a Whole Word With PHP 1 Comment I’ve been slacking an not writing anything so I’m going to start trying to write much smaller posts starting with this one. A common need for template developers is chopping a string at a whole word. There’s a lot of functions out there on the web to tackle this problem and I went searching for one quickly today rather than just writing one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Of Choice</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/editor-of-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 14:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/editor-of-choice/</guid>
      <description>Editor Of Choice I’m a pretty big fan of open source initiatives, code, rules, and especially software. If you go to school for computer science they’re going to give you the command line and probably a bunch of proprietary software; either free or not, to develop with. Sun puts out a decent developer JAVA. Microsoft has Visual Studio. And, if you’re as fortunate as me you’ll get to learn BASIC and you might even come upon a floppy with QBasic on it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New jQuery Content Rotator Plugin</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/new-jquery-content-rotator-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/new-jquery-content-rotator-plugin/</guid>
      <description>New jQuery Content Rotator Plugin This is an official release of a jQuery plugin I wrote some time ago and have been using and updating a lot lately. I’ve decided to release it here, and on jQuery, because I’ve finally got all of the bugs out and it has enough options and methods to work for any job. As devlopers we get a lot of requests for some image slideshow or content slideshow at the top of the homepage or some subsequent page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Framework Roundup</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/mobile-framework-roundup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/mobile-framework-roundup/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Framework Roundup I’ve been working at this office in Bakersfield for about 2 years now after my foray into the freelance world which I did also for 2 years. And while I still freelance on the side it’s nice to work with a team of people I see everyday. It also provides me the opportunity to start taking more time out and writing about the work I do and things I love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Protecting HTML Files</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/password-protecting-html-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/password-protecting-html-files/</guid>
      <description>Password Protecting HTML Files The other day I was doing some work on a back-end system for a client and ran into the problem of having a ton of html files that needed to be accessible only by administrators. Why would I have a bunch of html files you ask? For practical reasons you may have any number of files you don.t want displayed on the web to just anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending Emails That Don&#39;t Suck With WordPress</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/sending-email-that-dont-suck-with-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/sending-email-that-dont-suck-with-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Sending Emails That Don’t Suck With WordPress I’ve wondered about emailing in WordPress for a while but never did anything about it. How does WordPress send emails? What functions can we hook to for emails? What if I want to setup a template with a form and email someone? And, what if I want to send nice html emails and not just plain-text formatted ones? These are all good questions and definitely what I have been wondering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Variable Scope</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/understanding-variable-scope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/understanding-variable-scope/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Variable Scope This week I saw a lot of problems on forums, and at our office related to scope. So I’ve decided to write on scope as it relates to a few languages and discuss why understanding variable scope can save you a lot of headache. I know there are already quite a few articles online about it; but while most only discuss how to keep variables in scope and use them, most don’t talk about the importance of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIR3 In Flash CS5 For iOS / Android</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/air3-in-flash-cs5-for-ios-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 16:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/air3-in-flash-cs5-for-ios-android/</guid>
      <description>AIR3 In Flash CS5 For iOS / Android Still slacking. But I just thought about this blog and thought I would put up my recent troubles.
Adobe has been touting lately that the new version of AIR is so powerful that people are porting over intense Flash games for iOS. Being an avid AS3 developer I didn’t want to miss out on testing AIR for iOS and Android both. We’ve been able to do development for both these platforms for nearly 2 years now so I’m not going to tell you anything revolutionary or cutting edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AS3 Remoting Class &amp; AMFPHP</title>
      <link>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/as3-remoting-class-amfphp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 16:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mneilsworld.com/post/as3-remoting-class-amfphp/</guid>
      <description>AS3 Remoting Class &amp;amp; AMFPHP So if you haven’t heard; AMFPHP has been a big deal. With Flex doing all of Flash’s heavy data lifting lately it’s been a real, crying, egregious shame that Adobe has left out the Remoting Components from AS2. Although, I’m not going to just sit here and ramble on about how Flash is still more than capable of remoting and how tons of people are still doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>